<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Vaibhav Pathak</title>
    <link>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Vaibhav Pathak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:11:26 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Use Kong API Gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/why-use-kong-api-gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:11:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/why-use-kong-api-gateway/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kong API Gateway is a cloud-native API gateway that is based on the Nginx reverse proxy. It is a simple, fast, and lightweight solution that enables you to control, set up, and direct application-to-dedicated server request routing. The Kong API Gateway helps regulate who can access the services and data that are managed behind it. It ensures data security by allowing only authorized users and apps to access the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Own VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/running-own-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/running-own-vpn/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Of course, we all do know what is VPN and why we need one. Here I am not going to explain to you guys what is VPN and how it works and all. Here I am going to talk about how you can set up your own VPN server in any geographic location.
Recently I moved to a new country. But after arriving here I realised that now I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to watch all my digital content like web series, movies and some mobile applications which work in my home country only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Kubernetes on RHEL 7.9</title>
      <link>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/running-kubernetes-on-rhel-7.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 17:31:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vaibhavp.dev/blog/running-kubernetes-on-rhel-7.9/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We know what is Kubernetes and how much it&amp;rsquo;s important in today&amp;rsquo;s world of micro-services. So today we are going to see how to create a Kubernetes cluster on Red Hat Linux 7. For this tutorial we are going to use RHEL 7.9 version.
In this Kubernetes cluster we are just going to have only one node cluster i.e. we will use kubeadm tool to install all Kubernetes master node components on single node.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
